Guide to the Lucien L. Nunn papers [ca.1863-1971]
Nunn, Lucien L. papers [ca.1863-1971]
- Series III. Telluride Power Company and the Power Industry
  - TPC: Miscellany
    - Notecard index reference address file A-R (Box 31)
    - Notecard index reference address file S-Z (Box 32)
  - TPC: Beaver River Power Company
    - Correspondence, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Incorporation, Consolidation, Name Change & Amendments, 1917-1937 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Map (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Map: Plot of River in Beaver County (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Engineering Report by Telluride Institute, May 1908 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Engineering Report by Telluride Institute, February 1, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Legal Brief (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Legal Brief and Related Correspondence, 1915 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Settlement Documents, Dec. 1912-April 1913 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - TPC: Big Springs Power Company
    - Financial Records, Correspondence & Meeting Minutes, 1936-1945 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Financial Records, Correspondence (including REA Controversy) & Meeting Minutes, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Financial Records, Correspondence & Meeting Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Financial Records & Meeting Minutes, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - TPC: Ontario Power Company
    - Address by P.N. Nunn (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Agreements (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Agreement between Ontario Power Co. of Niagara Falls and the Niagara, Lockport and Ontario Power Co., July 16, 1904 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence & Documents (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Mortgage, Feb. 2, 1903 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Photograph of Niagara Power Model (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Publications (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Recommendations for Niagara Falls, Ontario Prepared by Telluride Association (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Report on Niagara Falls (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Statutes and Agreements (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Statistics (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - TPC: The Power Co. - Norris, Montana
    - Correspondence & Memos (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Maps & Blueprints I (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Maps & Blueprints II (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Reports & Notes (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - TPC: Wyoming Electric
    - Correspondence about Financial Matters, 1916-1919 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence between Charles Marks and F.C. Noon, 1917-1919 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Electric Rate Schedules, 1915, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Report, Aug. 1, 1915 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - TPC: Its Predecessor - San Miguel Consolidated Gold Mining Company
    - Agreement with Westinghouse Electric (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Amendments (copies) (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Paper (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Records, Articles of Incorporation, By-Laws and Meeting Minutes (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Records, Articles of Incorporation, By-Laws and Meeting Minutes (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - "Statement A" Furnished to H.A. Orth (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Stock Certificates (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - TPC: Its Successor - Utah Power & Light Company
    - Annual Report, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Articles & Brochures, 1943-1956 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Banquet Program, October 1937 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Cadet Training Course (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 1939-1943 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence with Telluride Association, 1941-1959 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Employee Information Program, February 5, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Financial Reports & Statements, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Historical File - Personnel Department (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - "History of Utah Power & Light and Affiliated Companies" (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - News Clippings (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - "Northwest Interconnected Systems" (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Stock Certificates (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - "Utah's First Century", 1951 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Utah Power & Ligth Co. v. United States, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Utah Securities Corp. Financial and Physical Data, March 31, 1915 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Utah Securities Corp. Organizational Chart (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Photographs of Power Development (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Settlement Documents, Dec. 1913-March 1913 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Settlement Documents, April 1913 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Settlement Documents, May 1913 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - TPC: Telluride Institute
    - General
      - Articles of Incorporation, 1904-1911 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Applications (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Class Records, 1908-1910 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence & Documents - Clem Cordray (Pinhead) (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence - Clem Cordray (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence re: Clem Cordray's Death, 1908 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Envelope (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Fellowship Form (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Financial Records - Frank Noon Account (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Financial Statements, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Report by A.L. Woodhouse - Off the Record (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Reunions, 1906-1909 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Scholarship Information (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Teacher's Improved Class Book, 1912 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Ames Branch (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Battle Creek Branch (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Boise, Idaho Branch (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Boise, Idaho Branch - Book Bulletin, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Bliss Branch (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Colorado Branches (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Grace, Idaho Branch, 1909-1910 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Grace, Idaho Branch, 1911-1912 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Grace, Idaho Branch (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Grace, Idaho Branch - Student Body (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Illium Branch (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Illium Branch - Proposed Quarters Bueprint (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Logan Branch (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Beaver Branch
      - Beaver Branch #1 I (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - Beaver Branch #1 II (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Beaver Branch #1 III (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - Beaver Branch #2 I (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - Beaver Branch #2 II (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - Beaver Branch #2 III (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - Beaver Branch #3 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - Beaver Branch #4 I, 1915-1917 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - Beaver Branch #4 II, 1915-1917 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      - Beaver Branch - Harlequin Transcripts I (Box 8, Folder 38)
      - Beaver Branch - Harlequin Transcripts II (Box 8, Folder 39)
      - Beaver Harlequin (Box 8, Folder 40)
      - Beaver Harlequin (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - Beaver Harlequin (copies) (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - Beaver Harlequin - New Years, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - Beaver Branch - Roll Book of Thos. S. Haddaway, 1911-1912 (Box 8, Folder 44)
      - Beaver Branch - Superintendent Reports, 1914-1915 (Box 8, Folder 45)
      - Beaver Branch - Superintendent Reports, 1916-1917 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Beaver Branch - C.A. Tozer, Superintendent (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Olmstead Branch
      - Olmstead Branch (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Olmstead Branch - Olmstead Census I, 1906-1912 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Olmstead Branch - Olmstead Census II, 1906-1912 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Olmstead Branch - Olmstead Census III, 1906-1912 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Olmstead Branch - Olmstead Census IV, 1906-1912 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Olmstead Branch - Olmstead Census, 1908-1909 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Olmstead Branch - Christmas, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Olmstead Branch - Correspondence & Documents, 1950-1957 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Olmstead Branch - Construction I (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Olmstead Branch - Construction II (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Olmstead Branch - Grant of Authority, Constitution & By-Laws, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Olmstead Branch - Lectures on Hydraulics, 1910-1911 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Olmstead Branch - Ledger - Discipline Committee (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Olmstead Branch - Ledger - Discipline Committee (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Olmstead Branch - Ledger - Leave of Absence Committee (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Olmstead Branch - Ledger - Leave of Absence Committee (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Olmstead Branch - Ledger - Student Body [Financial Records] (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Olmstead Branch - Ledger - Time In/Out (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Olmstead Branch - Meeting Minutes, 1909-1911 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Olmstead Branch - Plans (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Olmstead Branch - Student Body I (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - Olmstead Branch - Student Body II (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - Olmstead Branch - Student Body III (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Olmstead Branch - Student Body IV (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - Olmstead Branch - Student Body V (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - Olmstead Branch - Student Body VI (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - Olmstead Branch - Student Body VII (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - Olmstead Branch - Student Body VIII (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - Olmstead Branch - Student Body Minutes (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Other Power Industry Companies
    - Dawson Electric Company - Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Great Falls Power Company - Charter & Organization (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Knight Power Company, Provo, Utah (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Mount Whitney Power Company - Report by Telluride Institute, 1906 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Niagara Power Company - "The Utilization of Niagara," by Thomas Commerford Martin (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Power & Light Company - Dave Johnston Steam-Electric Plant, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Southern Pacific Company - Correspondenc, Documents & Blueprints (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Electric Bond & Share Company - Settlement Documents, January 1913 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Idaho-Nevada Power Company - Settlement Documents, April 1913 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Settlement Documents (copies) (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Weleetka Water Power & Washita Electric Power Comany - Report (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Power Industry Publications
    - Adventures in Power: A Fact History of Westinghouse (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - European Hydro-Electric Power Development by Charles H. Mitchell (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - George Westinghouse, His Life and Achievements by Leupp (mutilated copy), 1918 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Government & Legal, 1881-1894 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Government & Legal, 1906 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Government & Legal, 1908 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Government & Legal, 1909 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Government & Legal, 1910 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Government & Legal, 1911 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Government & Legal, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Government & Legal, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Government & Legal, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Government & Legal, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Government & Legal, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - A Life of George Westinghouse by Henry G. Prout (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - List of publications by Herbert J. Reich (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Looking Squarely at the Water Problem by Henry J. Pierce, n.d (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Journal of Electricity Power & Gas and accompanying letter to L.L. Nunn, July 17, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous Pamphlets and Periodicals (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1893, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - M.A.N. Dieselmotoren-Nachrichten and letter, July 1958 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Pipe Lines for Hydraulic Power Plants by Arthur Jobson (presented before Telluride Institute), June 22, 1907 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Present Status of the Transmission and Distribution of Electrical Energy by Louis Duncan (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Scenes from a Great Life: George Westinghouse Centennial, 1846-1946 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Electrical World and Electrical Engineer - Copies (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Power Industry Miscellany
    - Correspondence & Documents - Supreme Court/Public Land Policy (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence re: Utah v. Sweet / Document re: Power of Congress to Dispose of Public Lands, 1910, July 26, 1866 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence - Electrical Historical Foundation (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Federal Power Commission Inventory, Telluride District I, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Federal Power Commission Inventory, Telluride District II, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Federal Power Commission Inventory, Telluride District III, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Speech - Reminiscences of Early Electrical Development by M.E. Buck, June 1, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Publications: Information Booklets on Electric Plants and Supply Companies, 1903-1955 (Box 7, Folder 41)
      Includes: "State Historical Landmark No. 514 Pomona Water Plant" (1955), "Ouray: The Gem of the Rockies" (1903), "Adventures in Power: A Fact History of Westinghouse" (1936, two copies with slightly different format), "The Electrical Plant of the Ontario Power Company" (1906), "Allgemeine Elektricitaets-Gesellschaft Berlin" (1893)
    - Publications: Scientific Papers Published by Others, 1887-1958 (Box 7, Folder 42)
      Includes: "Distribution of Electricity by Secondary Generators" (1887), "Discriminating Lightning Arresters and Recent Progress in Means for Protection Against Lightning" (1894), "Harold P. Brown and the Executioner's Current: an Incident in the AC-DC Controversy" (1958), "The Maximum Distance to which Power can be Economically Transmitted" (1904), "Drop in Alternating Current Lines" (1897), "Polyphase Transmission" (1894), "The Induction Motor and the Rotary Converter and their Relation to the Transmission System" (1901), "Alternating-Current Development in America" (1912)
    - Westinghouse Electric Company Price List, 1890 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Hydro Power, 2014; DVD-2005 (Box 7)
      Excerpt from what was originally issued as disc 5 of the Rocky Mountain PBS series Colorado Experience, season 2. Describes how L.L. Nunn saved the mining business in Telluride, Colorado by financing the Ames Hydroelectric Generating Plant, the first in the world to generate alternating current electric power for industrial purposes. Soon hydroelectric plants appeared across the United States and the world.
- Series IV. Telluride Association
  - Alumni
    - Alumni, 1913-1951 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Survey, [1952] (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Survey, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Boston Area (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Chicago Area (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Cleveland (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Los Angeles Area (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - New York City (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Scattered (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Utah (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Washington Area (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Records Compiled by E.M. Johnson (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Committees
    - Adjustment Committee, 1915-1916 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Committee to Amend the Work Requirement Provision of the TA Constitution - Report (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Central Advisory Committee, 1915, 1939-1954 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Committee to Cooperate with Trustees of Deep Springs I, 1938-1947 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Committee to Cooperate with Trustees of Deep Springs II, 1938-1947 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Committee to Cooperate with Trustees of Deep Springs III, 1938-1947 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Judiciary Committee I, 1938-1955 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Judiciary Committee II, 1938-1955 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - New Funds Committee - Reports and Correspondence I, 1951-1957 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - New Funds Committee - Reports and Correspondence II, 1951-1957 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - New Funds Committee - List, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Permanent Financial Advisory Committee (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Scholarship Committee - Scholarship Record Card (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Solicitation Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Conventions
    - 1910 Pre-Constitutional Convention & Meetings before 1911 Convention (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Expense Bills of Delegates to 1910 Convention, August 12, 1910 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - 1911 Constitutional Convention - Olmstead, Utah, June 26- July 8, 1911 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - 1911 Constitutional Convention - Minutes, June 26- July 8, 1911 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - 1911 Constitutional Convention - Minutes, June 26- July 8, 1911 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - 1911 Constitutional Convention - Minutes & Committee Reports, June 26- July 8, 1911 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 1911 Constitutional Convention - Annotated By-laws, Constitution, & Correspondence I (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - 1911 Constitutional Convention - Annotated By-laws, Constitution, & Correspondence II (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - 1911 Constitutional Convention - Discussion Notebooks (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - 1911 Constitutional Convention - Dean Thornhill's Report (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - 1911 Constitutional Convention - Constitution Draft, Correspondence & Info on Property Transfer from Power Co.'s for the Establishment of TA (copies) (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Charter Members (June 3, 1911), Deed of Trust & Constitution - L.L. Nunn's Annotated Copies (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Engrossed (signed) Copy of TA Constitution, July 7, 1911 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - 2 Signed Copies of Deed of Property & Constitution, 1911 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Constitution Copies (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - History of Constitutional Convention - Correspondence & Documents collected by Orville Sweeting I (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - History of Constitutional Convention - Correspondence & Documents collected by Orville Sweeting II (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - History of Constitutional Convention - Correspondence & Documents collected by Orville Sweeting III (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - History of Constitutional Convention - Correspondence & Documents collected by Orville Sweeting IV (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - 1912-1914 - Proxy Voting Forms (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Some Convention files and photos have been digitized, 1911-1960; 1418
      Some Telluride Association newsletters and photographs from this collection are also available online here: http://ecommons.library.cornell.edu/handle/1813/29989
    - 1912 Convention (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - 1913 Convention (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - 1914-1916 Conventions - Treasurer's Documents (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - 1914 Convention (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - 1914 Convention - Minutes I (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - 1914 Convention - Minutes II (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - 1914 Convention - Minutes III (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - 1915 Convention I (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - 1915 Convention II (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - 1915 Convention - Dean's Report (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - 1916 Convention - Minutes (originals) (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - 1916 Convention - Minutes & Reports (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - 1916 Convention - P. Bailey's Correspondence, Attendance & Expense Records (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - 1917 Convention - Correspondence & Minutes (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - 1917 Convention - Annotated Minutes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - 1919-1922 Convention - Minutes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - 1923-1928 Convention - Minutes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - 1929-1934 Convention - Minutes (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - 1935-1939 Convention - Minutes (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - 1940-1943 Convention - Minutes (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - 1944-1947 Convention - Minutes (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - 1948-1949 Convention - Minutes (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - 1951-1953 Convention - Minutes (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - 1954-1956 Convention - Minutes (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - 1966-1967 Convention - Minutes (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - 1972 & 1974-1975 Convention - Minutes (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Corporation
    - Records I, 1949-1954 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Records II, 1949-1954 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Records, 1949-1956 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Telluride Corp. (TelCorp) critical documents (volume 1), 1948-1954 (Box 63)
    - Telluride Corp. (TelCorp) critical documents (volume 2), 1955-1973 (Box 63)
  - Correspondence & Documents
    - Correspondence, 1910 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1913-1917 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - Applicants (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - Ashworth, Paul P. & Dexter S. Kimball (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - Biersach, W.L. I (copies) (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - Biersach, W.L. II (copies) (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence - Biersach, W.L. I (copies), 1924-1926 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence - Biersach, W.L. II (copies), 1924-1926 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence - Biersach, W.L. III (copies), 1924-1926 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence - Biersach, W.L. (originals), 1915-1917 & 1924-1926 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence - Biersach, W.L. (originals), 1939-1941 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence - Cadman, Paul (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence - The Council, 1939-1948 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence & Documents - Fuller, Eugene (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence - Johnson, E.M., 1956 & 1961 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence - Members, 1912-1946 (bulk 1939-1946) (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence - Members, 1957-1960 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence - New York Telephone Co., 1909-1918 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence & Documents - Nightingale, L.G. "Doc", 1915-1932 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - Nunn, L.L. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - Sabine, George H., 1959 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - U.S. Immigration & Naturalization Service, 1935-1950 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence & Documents - re: Utah Fire and Clay Co. I (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence & Documents - re: Utah Fire and Clay Co. II (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence & Documents - re: Utah Fire and Clay Co. III (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence & Documents - re: Utah Fire and Clay Co. IV (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence & Documents - re: Utah Fire and Clay Co. V (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence & Documents - re: Utah Fire and Clay Co. VI (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence & Documents - re: Utah Fire and Clay Co. VII (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence & Documents - re: Utah Fire and Clay Co. VIII (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence & Documents - Van Supreme Court (NY) re: dispute over exemption of Ithaca, NY property from taxation I (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence & Documents - Van Supreme Court (NY) re: dispute over exemption of Ithaca, NY property from taxation II (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence & Documents - Van Supreme Court (NY) re: decision of TA tax status (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence & Documents - Walcott, Helen B. inquiring into applying for membership (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence & Documents - Walcott, Sidney S. I, 1910-1917 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence & Documents - Walcott, Sidney S. II, 1910-1917 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence & Documents - Walcott, Sidney S., 1909-1911 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - Walcott, Sidney S. I (copies), 1916-1917 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - Walcott, Sidney S. II (copies), 1916-1917 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - Waldo, H.R re: speech to Idaho Senate against Thomas Amendment (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence - Walker Bank, 1939-1940 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence - Whitman, C.N., 1910-1941 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence - Wrightington, S.R. (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence - Wrightington, S.R., H.R. Waldo & L. Nightingale, 1924-1925 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Custodians
    - Custodians I, 1939-1940 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Custodians II, 1939-1940 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Custodians I, 1947-1949 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Custodians II, 1947-1949 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Financial & Legal Records
    - Financial Records (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Financial Records I, 1911-1913 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Financial Records II, 1911-1913 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Financial Records III, 1911-1913 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Financial Records IV, 1911-1913 (Box 16, Folder 5)